gizdev.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy | GizDev

### **Your Privacy Is Our TOP Priority!!**

Hey there Gizdev visitors, We respect our user’s privacy, Our website collects some little information about you. When our users subscribe to our newsletters, registering on the site or maybe commenting on posts. So here we have written what information we collect about you when you visit our site. All user’s most know what information we collect about them. so here is the detailed description of our privacy policies.

####  **About The Browser Cookies:**

Our site Gizdev may use cookies Google as the third-party vendor uses the cookies for serving the ADS on our website. It does not collect any type of personal information that you may have a problem. Google uses cookies to serve better and appropriate ads according to your browsing history, sites visited by you etc. For more information about Google’s DART cookies refer **[HERE](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).  That’s how we use the cookies for your better experience on our site.**

####  **Advertising:**

Now, heading towards the advertising policy which concerned with your privacy directly or maybe indirectly. Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile nonpersonal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. **This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.**

####  **Electronic newsletters & Push Notification:**

If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list or Subscribed our Push Notification, they will receive that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. if any user wants to unsubscribe the newsletter & Push Notification they can. We never send any spam emails. We will collect your email address for sending our newsletter directly to your inbox time to time. We are using onesignal for Push Notification service, YES onesignal store cookies you can check their privacy policy from this link ⇒ <https://onesignal.com/privacy_policy>.

####  **Use Of Your Collected information:**

We believe in 100% user’s satisfaction and for reaching this goal we need some information about you. This information could be like if you subscribe newsletter comments on posts or use some our site resources. We will use your information to serve you better. We are trying continuously to improve our website. For that, we need some of our user’s information that will help us to gain a complete user satisfaction. Also, this information will help us to provide you best services possible by us.

####  **Your Information Is Safe With Us:**

Don’t worry about the information we collect about you. It is protected by our secure servers. Most importantly we don’t sell or trade any information about you to anyone. Only generic information is shared with our trusted ones. We also clean your data annually.

####  **File Hosting sites:**

We share lots of contents with all of our users. For providing this content we share the links on our secure Filehosting servers. The use of cookies will be as per to file hosting sites. We assure you your information will not be any harm because of any of them. We always provide content on our only trusted and secure file hosting servers.

####  **Important Note:**

We do not collect any of the information of the children who are under the age of 1. All the information policy applied to ones which are more than 13 years old. This online privacy will only affect or apply for the information collected from our websites only. It does not apply the information collected offline.

####  **Acceptance Of The Policy:**

By using our site, you accept our privacy policy and all the points stated above.

####  **Changes To Privacy Policy:**

If we ever decide to change our privacy policy, we will post about the changes on this privacy policy page only.

####  **Have Questions? Contact Us:**

If you have any questions or queries regarding the privacy policy above you can [contact us](https://www.gizdev.com/contact/) at  **admin@gizdev.com.**
